[Music]
Sunlife is a leading financial services
company that helps clients achieve
lifetime financial security and live
healthier lives.
Since 1865,
no matter in good times or bad times,
SunLife always stands side by side with
our clients, accompanying them through
the most important moments in life.
Today, Sunlife serves 10 millions of
clients in Canada, the US, Asia, the UK,
and other parts of the world. We are the
number one provider of retirement
solutions in Canada. For 133 years,
Sunlife has supported Asia's growth.
Sunlife was the first multinational life
insurance company established in Hong
Kong. Today, we are one of the leaders
in the market and we were one of the few
insurance companies approved for early
RBC regime adoption. One in every eight
Hong Kong residents is a Sunlife client,
making us the third largest mandatory
provident fund provider in the market.
Our insurance business is regulated by
the regulators under three major
governments of Hong Kong, Canada, and
Bermuda.
Throughout our 160year history, our
clients and investors have benefited
from Sunlife's ability to be a stable
force and navigate uncertainty.
During the 1918 Spanish flu outbreak,
Sunlife paid out $2.1 million US in
claims.
When London was attacked during World
War II, Sunlife helped the British
government safeguard 5 billion in assets
by storing them in the company's vault
in Canada.
Despite the economic turmoil of the
global financial crisis, Sunlife
remained among the world's strongest
insurance companies with a strong
capital position.
During the CO 19 outbreak, Sunlife has
paid more than1 billion Canadian dollars
in claims and donated $2 million US to
help fight the pandemic.
Globally, we continue to support the
underprivileged groups in our
communities through local food banks,
elderly care, and medical services. You
can count on us in everchanging times.
Sunlife has been awarded top financial
strength rating of AA by Standard and
Pors.
Our shares are traded on the stock
exchanges in Toronto, New York, and the
Philippines.
With 28 offices around the world, 66,900
employees, and 95,000 advisers,
Sunlife assists more than 85 million
clients globally with comprehensive
financial and health solutions.
Sunlife is one of the world's largest
asset management companies with 1.54
trillion Canadian dollars in assets
under management. In Hong Kong, we have
steadily increased the total assets
under management to more than 8.63
trillion Hong Kong dollars, accounting
for more than 1/5if of the total asset
value of China's insurance industry.
Sunlife manages assets through its five
major asset management companies and
advisers asset management which provides
individual high- netw worth investors
access to alternative investment
products in the US. Sunlife using
leading investment strategies that aim
to create stable long-term returns for
clients.
MFS investment management has over $66
billion in AUM. Its operational profit
ranked top 25 percentile gainer among
top tier asset management companies.
SLC management comprises five specialty
managers
including SLC fixed income,
Crescent Capital Group which invests in
and manages private credit assets.
BGO which focuses on real estate
investment. Infrared Capital Partners,
which manages over 200 infrastructure
investment projects, and Advisers Asset
Management, which is one of the largest
investment solutions platforms in the
US.
Sunlife has a diversified investment
portfolio with strong performance. Over
99% of the debt securities investment
are rated BBB minus or higher,
indicating investment grade. For 16
consecutive years, Sunlife has been
named one of the Corporate Knights
global 100 most sustainable companies,
ranking first among Canadian insurance
companies. We achieved our goal of 20
billion Canadian dollars in new
sustainable investments between 2021 and
2025.
For 133 years, Sunlife has worked to
build a better future for our clients
and communities.
Working in partnership to help our
clients achieve lifetime financial
security and live healthier lives.